<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<doi_batch xmlns="http://www.crossref.org/schema/4.4.2"
           xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
           xmlns:jats="http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/JATS1"
           version="4.4.2"
           xsi:schemaLocation="https://data.crossref.org/reports/help/schema_doc/doi_resources4.4.2/index.html http://data.crossref.org/schemas/crossref4.4.2.xsd">
   <head>
      <doi_batch_id>20200429110735773</doi_batch_id>
      <timestamp>20200429110735773</timestamp>
      <depositor>
         <depositor_name>Heather Westerlund</depositor_name>
         <email_address>heather.westerlund@mail.waldenu.edu</email_address>
      </depositor>
      <registrant>Walden University</registrant>
   </head>
   <body>
      <journal>
         <journal_metadata>
            <full_title>Journal of Educational Research and Practice</full_title>
            <abbrev_title>JERAP</abbrev_title>
            <issn media_type="electronic">2167-8693</issn>
         </journal_metadata>
         <journal_issue>
            <publication_date media_type="online">
               <month>04</month>
               <day>17</day>
               <year>2020</year>
            </publication_date>
            <journal_volume>
               <volume>10</volume>
            </journal_volume>
            <issue>1</issue>
         </journal_issue>
         <journal_article publication_type="full_text">
            <titles>
               <title>Discipline Policies and Preschool Special Education Students'
								Personal-Social Skills</title>
            </titles>
            <contributors>
               <person_name sequence="first" contributor_role="author">
                  <given_name>Amanda L.</given_name>
                  <surname>Tamagni</surname>
                  <affiliation>Walden University</affiliation>
               </person_name>
               <person_name sequence="additional" contributor_role="author">
                  <given_name>Andrea M.</given_name>
                  <surname>Wilson</surname>
                  <affiliation>Walden University</affiliation>
               </person_name>
            </contributors>
            <jats:abstract>
               <jats:p>Preschool special education students’ lack of personal–social skills is affecting their kindergarten readiness and placing them at risk for exposure to school discipline in a large school district in the Southeastern United States. The purpose of this quantitative investigation was to examine the relationship between the quality of school discipline policies and personal–social skills of preschool special education students within the focus district. Data collection included archived personal–social skills scores, as measured by the Battelle Developmental Inventory–2 (BDI-2), of 354 preschool special education students. Four trained educators rated the effectiveness of the schools’ discipline policies using the Teaching and Guidance Policy Essentials Checklist (TAGPEC). Preschool special education students’ personal–social skills were measured using the BDI-2, and discipline policies were measured using the TAGPEC. Findings from simple linear regression analysis indicated no significant relationship between the TAGPEC ratings and students’ BDI-2 scores. The personal–social skills for students in Title I and non-Title I schools (&lt;em&gt;n &lt;/em&gt;= 96 students per group) were compared while controlling for TAGPEC ratings, but results showed no statistically significant differences. The average quality of the discipline policies was rated as inadequate overall. A policy recommendation was developed to encourage effective discipline policies and create a supportive school environment to promote positive social behaviors of all students, including the youngest and most vulnerable.</jats:p>
            </jats:abstract>
            <publication_date media_type="online">
               <month>04</month>
               <day>17</day>
               <year>2020</year>
            </publication_date>
            <doi_data>
               <doi>10.5590/JERAP.2020.10.1.03</doi>
               <resource>https://scholarworks.waldenu.edu/jerap/vol10/iss1/3</resource>
               <collection property="crawler-based">
                  <item crawler="iParadigms">
                     <resource>https://scholarworks.waldenu.edu/cgi/viewcontent.cgi?article=1471&amp;amp;context=jerap&amp;amp;unstamped=1</resource>
                  </item>
               </collection>
            </doi_data>
         </journal_article>
         <journal_article publication_type="full_text">
            <titles>
               <title>Mentoring Secondary Novice Teachers to Develop Academic Language
								of English Language Learners</title>
            </titles>
            <contributors>
               <person_name sequence="first" contributor_role="author">
                  <given_name>Susan</given_name>
                  <surname>O'Hara</surname>
                  <affiliation>University of California, Davis, Davis, California,
										United States</affiliation>
               </person_name>
               <person_name sequence="additional" contributor_role="author">
                  <given_name>Joanne</given_name>
                  <surname>Bookmyer</surname>
                  <affiliation>University of California, Davis, Davis, California,
										United States</affiliation>
               </person_name>
               <person_name sequence="additional" contributor_role="author">
                  <given_name>Robert</given_name>
                  <surname>Pritchard</surname>
                  <affiliation>EPF for Teaching, Sacramento, California, United
										States</affiliation>
               </person_name>
               <person_name sequence="additional" contributor_role="author">
                  <given_name>Robin</given_name>
                  <surname>Martin</surname>
                  <affiliation>University of California, Davis, Davis, California,
										United States</affiliation>
               </person_name>
            </contributors>
            <jats:abstract>
               <jats:p>This exploratory, qualitative study examines the foundational knowledge and instructional methods needed for academic language teaching of English language learners (ELLs). It also examines how mentoring practices can build secondary content-based novice teachers’ instructional capacity in this area. The study uses synthesized data from two independent studies to contextualize findings on essential instructional practices within the process of mentoring new teachers. Three themes emerged: novices need the foundational, theoretical and practical knowledge underlying essential practices for academic language development; essential practices must be articulated in detail for enactment by teachers; and balancing explicit and immersive academic language instruction is a major paradigm shift for novices. Implications for mentor and teacher professional development are discussed, as mentors are key to supporting the uptake of dynamic instructional methods needed to enact essential practices. While mentoring is a common strategy for supporting new teachers, few models exist for how mentors can support new teachers with building the academic language development of ELLs. Further, few studies examine mentoring exchanges that can promote teachers’ understanding and practices to support ELL students’ academic language development. Limitations of the study include sample size and use of varied respondent data sets.</jats:p>
            </jats:abstract>
            <publication_date media_type="online">
               <month>03</month>
               <day>27</day>
               <year>2020</year>
            </publication_date>
            <doi_data>
               <doi>10.5590/JERAP.2020.10.1.02</doi>
               <resource>https://scholarworks.waldenu.edu/jerap/vol10/iss1/2</resource>
               <collection property="crawler-based">
                  <item crawler="iParadigms">
                     <resource>https://scholarworks.waldenu.edu/cgi/viewcontent.cgi?article=1347&amp;amp;context=jerap&amp;amp;unstamped=1</resource>
                  </item>
               </collection>
            </doi_data>
         </journal_article>
         <journal_article publication_type="full_text">
            <titles>
               <title>PreK–5 Teacher Views of Professional Development Integrating
								Common Core Language Arts With Science and Social Studies</title>
            </titles>
            <contributors>
               <person_name sequence="first" contributor_role="author">
                  <given_name>Janie</given_name>
                  <surname>Hubbard</surname>
                  <affiliation>The University of Alabama</affiliation>
               </person_name>
               <person_name sequence="additional" contributor_role="author">
                  <given_name>Melisa</given_name>
                  <surname>Fowler</surname>
                  <affiliation>The University of Alabama</affiliation>
               </person_name>
               <person_name sequence="additional" contributor_role="author">
                  <given_name>Lee</given_name>
                  <surname>Freeman</surname>
                  <affiliation>The University of Alabama</affiliation>
               </person_name>
            </contributors>
            <jats:abstract>
               <jats:p>Three preK–6 U.S. university methods instructors-researchers (literacy, science, social studies) joined 17 Title I school teachers for collaborative lesson planning and teaching within the preK–5 school setting. Each team’s goal was to create and teach interdisciplinary curriculum units using U.S. English language arts Common Core State Standards with social studies and science. A year-long instrumental case study design was used to examine (a) how teachers perceived collaborative professional development to create interdisciplinary unit plans and (b) how teachers viewed outcomes of teaching interdisciplinary units of their own design. Practice articles regarding Common Core State Standards curricula integration are plentiful; however, this study offers researched insights.Collectively, research from various locations and school cultures benefits those needing to structure realistic professional development designs.</jats:p>
            </jats:abstract>
            <publication_date media_type="online">
               <month>03</month>
               <day>09</day>
               <year>2020</year>
            </publication_date>
            <doi_data>
               <doi>10.5590/JERAP.2020.10.1.01</doi>
               <resource>https://scholarworks.waldenu.edu/jerap/vol10/iss1/1</resource>
               <collection property="crawler-based">
                  <item crawler="iParadigms">
                     <resource>https://scholarworks.waldenu.edu/cgi/viewcontent.cgi?article=1438&amp;amp;context=jerap&amp;amp;unstamped=1</resource>
                  </item>
               </collection>
            </doi_data>
         </journal_article>
      </journal>
   </body>
</doi_batch>
